This film was shot in 1912 and due to
the equipment used at the time it has no soundtrack
THE WAR FOR INDEPENDENCE
The Romanian -Russian - Turkish war 1877
Shot with the help of the Romanian Army
and the artists of the Bucharest National Theatre.
During peace time
(in the village)
The country was in danger
His Highness the king Carol I of Romania decrees
the mobilization of the army.
The mobilization.
Penes and Rodica
We were 9 when we left the town of Vaslui
At Calafat.
Cobuz's Death.
This is the music that I like!
Over the Danube
Russians repelled by the Turks.
Posing the new flags.
The Turks gathered a lot of troops at Plevna
and they are crushing us.
Cross the Danube any way you want.
Nicolas.
Religious ceremony for the flags.
Distributing the new flags.
Crossing the Danube
19th - 20th of July 1877
The patrols cross.
Building the bridge.
His Highness the Tsar of the Russians entrusted me
with the supreme command of both allied armies
operating around Plevna.
Make our ancestors flag rise again remembering
the glorious days of Michael the Brave
and Stephen the Great.
Proceed, troops, trusting God for our right,
for the Romanian Independence.
Carol.
The embarking.
The landing.
The main landing.
James and Carl is in the fight.
The pursuit of the Turks.
The attack.
A Turkish patrol.
Osman Pasha, the commander of the
Turkish army at Plevna.
The Romanians were repelled.
His Highness King Carol encourages them.
"Through fire and smoke..."
Claiming Grivita the first time.
The soldier Grigore Ioan takes the Turkish flag.
Consigning the flag.
The Russian attack at the Green Mountains.
General Skobeleff.
The valley of despair.
The cease-fire.
Burying the dead.
His Highness the Tsar Alexander the Second
and His Highness King Carol I
visit the wounded.
Fighting around Plevna.
A Turkish attack.
Go! Go! Go!
The fall of Plevna
28th of November 1877.
The Turks leaving Plevna.
Crossing the river Vid.
The Turkish attack.
The Russian position.
The Romanian intervention.
Osman Pasha was wounded.
The main attack.
Opanez.
His Highness King Carol I follows the battle.
The Cavalry attack.
The Infantry attack.
The Turks surrender.
The chaos.
After the fall of Plevna
Osman Pasha surrenders his sword.
His Highness Tsar Alexander II
gives back the sword to
Osman Pasha.
Osman Pasha's departure.
The sad convoy.
"On the hilly road"
After 35 years
Celebrating
the Romanian Independence.
THE END
translated and subtitled by finix