The plot focuses on the lives of the soon to be married <PERSON>Stefan</PERSON> (<PERSON>Felix Klare</PERSON>), a German working in <LOCATION>Romania</LOCATION> for a wealthy and eccentric printing company owner, <PERSON>Nicu Iorga</PERSON> (<PERSON>Răzvan Vasilescu</PERSON>) and his soon-to-be bride <PERSON>Brindusa</PERSON> (<PERSON>Alexandra Maria Lara</PERSON>), who is <PERSON>Nicu</PERSON>'s secretary. Life seems great for both of them, despite the eminent long affair that <PERSON>Nicu</PERSON> had with <PERSON>Brindusa</PERSON>. All the preparations are made for the wedding, <PERSON>Stefan</PERSON>'s family arrives, and the son-to-be bride and groom buy their wedding attire. A newly arrived German (who was set to replace <PERSON>Stefan</PERSON> at the printing company due to a fight with <PERSON>Nicu</PERSON>) <PERSON>Peter Gross</PERSON> (<PERSON>Bruno Cathomas</PERSON>) is invited to the wedding after he becomes friends with both <PERSON>Stefan</PERSON> and <PERSON>Brindusa</PERSON>. <PERSON>Nicu</PERSON>, armed with a gun (and accompanied by several henchmen), crashes the wedding ceremony and threatens everyone present, including <PERSON>Stefan</PERSON>'s father <PERSON>Ernst</PERSON> (<PERSON>Manfred Zapatka</PERSON>) and <PERSON>Brindusa</PERSON>'s father Mr. <PERSON>Hergehelegiu</PERSON>. He even punches <PERSON>Peter</PERSON> in the nose, after which he shoots himself and is taken to the hospital. At the hospital, <PERSON>Brindusa</PERSON> tells <PERSON>Stefan</PERSON> that he should go to <LOCATION>Germany</LOCATION> to pursue a better life, revealing to him that she still has feelings for <PERSON>Nicu</PERSON>. Although it is not stated in the movie, it is assumed <PERSON>Nicu</PERSON> survives the gunshot. The film ends with an enraged <PERSON>Stefan</PERSON> asking <PERSON>Peter</PERSON> about his nose just outside the hospital, after which they go down the road.