Having	O
recently	O
taken	O
over	O
the	O
role	O
of	O
entertainments	O
officer	O
at	O
an	O
army	O
camp	O
the	O
Padre	O
Captain	O
William	PERSON
Paris	PERSON
is	O
disheartened	O
so	O
few	O
of	O
the	O
troops	O
turn	O
out	O
for	O
an	O
evening	O
of	O
classical	O
music	O
.	O

He	O
visits	O
a	O
local	O
pub	O
and	O
finds	O
the	O
place	O
packed	O
with	O
soldiers	O
,	O
including	O
his	O
own	O
driver	O
.	O

He	O
then	O
resolves	O
to	O
try	O
and	O
secure	O
something	O
more	O
entertaining	O
for	O
the	O
troops	O
and	O
comes	O
up	O
with	O
the	O
idea	O
of	O
bringing	O
in	O
a	O
Brain	O
Trust	O
to	O
answer	O
questions	O
from	O
the	O
audience.With	O
the	O
help	O
of	O
Lady	O
Dodds	O
the	O
Captain	O
manages	O
to	O
gather	O
together	O
a	O
group	O
of	O
local	O
notables	O
,	O
who	O
all	O
swiftly	O
prove	O
to	O
be	O
mildly	O
eccentric	O
.	O

The	O
group	O
includes	O
the	O
opinionated	O
Professor	O
Mutch	PERSON
,	O
who	O
is	O
a	O
popular	O
radio	O
personality	O
with	O
the	O
BBC	ORGANIZATION
,	O
and	O
his	O
friend	O
the	O
oil	O
painter	O
George	PERSON
Prout	PERSON
and	O
his	O
wife	O
Angela	PERSON
.	O

While	O
arriving	O
at	O
their	O
house	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
interrupts	O
Mutch	PERSON
and	O
Mrs	PERSON
Prout	PERSON
who	O
are	O
about	O
to	O
embrace	O
.	O

Upon	O
meeting	O
Mr	O
Prout	PERSON
he	O
soon	O
finds	O
him	O
a	O
cold	O
man	O
who	O
verbally	O
abuses	O
his	O
wife	O
.	O

The	O
Trust	O
is	O
rounded	O
out	O
by	O
the	O
wandered	O
Doctor	O
McAdam	PERSON
and	O
the	O
chippy	O
local	O
Labour	ORGANIZATION
MP	O
Joseph	PERSON
Byres.With	PERSON
the	O
help	O
of	O
his	O
secretary	O
,	O
Private	O
Jessie	PERSON
Killigrew	PERSON
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
manages	O
to	O
organise	O
the	O
event	O
.	O

The	O
hall	O
is	O
relatively	O
well	O
filled	O
.	O

Trying	O
to	O
avoid	O
anything	O
controversial	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
forbids	O
any	O
discussion	O
of	O
politics	O
and	O
begins	O
with	O
some	O
innocuous	O
questions	O
about	O
cows	O
chasing	O
after	O
trains	O
and	O
if	O
the	O
Moon	O
is	O
inhabited	O
?	O

Things	O
soon	O
become	O
heated	O
when	O
the	O
MP	O
takes	O
offence	O
at	O
comments	O
directed	O
at	O
him	O
and	O
threatens	O
to	O
start	O
a	O
fight	O
.	O

Having	O
only	O
just	O
averted	O
this	O
,	O
a	O
question	O
about	O
marriage	O
reveals	O
the	O
fragility	O
of	O
the	O
Prout	O
's	O
marriage	O
.	O

Fearing	O
any	O
controversy	O
,	O
the	O
Captain	O
quickly	O
announces	O
that	O
it	O
is	O
time	O
for	O
the	O
interval.As	O
word	O
spreads	O
around	O
the	O
camp	O
of	O
the	O
goings-on	O
,	O
the	O
second	O
half	O
begins	O
with	O
the	O
room	O
completely	O
packed	O
.	O

The	O
Captain	O
tries	O
to	O
steer	O
the	O
debate	O
back	O
to	O
harmless	O
questions	O
about	O
bluebottles	O
,	O
but	O
the	O
audience	O
demands	O
an	O
answer	O
to	O
the	O
earlier	O
question	O
about	O
marriage	O
.	O

As	O
the	O
Prouts	O
begin	O
arguing	O
once	O
again	O
,	O
Mrs	PERSON
Prout	PERSON
admits	O
that	O
the	O
Professor	O
is	O
her	O
lover	O
.	O

At	O
this	O
the	O
whole	O
event	O
threatens	O
to	O
descend	O
into	O
anarchy	O
despite	O
the	O
attempts	O
of	O
the	O
Captain	O
to	O
maintain	O
order	O
.	O

Desperate	O
to	O
restore	O
a	O
sense	O
of	O
propriety	O
he	O
draws	O
the	O
proceedings	O
to	O
a	O
close	O
,	O
and	O
announces	O
that	O
next	O
week	O
they	O
will	O
return	O
to	O
classical	O
music	O
by	O
inviting	O
a	O
string	O
quartet	O
.	O

A	O
soldier	O
stands	O
up	O
and	O
thanks	O
the	O
Captain	O
for	O
providing	O
such	O
entertainment	O
and	O
asking	O
if	O
the	O
Brain	O
Trust	O
can	O
be	O
made	O
a	O
regular	O
feature.Worried	O
about	O
Mr	O
Prout	PERSON
who	O
has	O
disappeared	O
and	O
has	O
been	O
drinking	O
heavily	O
,	O
the	O
others	O
follow	O
him	O
back	O
to	O
his	O
house	O
where	O
they	O
mistakenly	O
believe	O
that	O
he	O
is	O
going	O
to	O
throw	O
himself	O
over	O
the	O
cliffs	O
.	O

Instead	O
he	O
is	O
planning	O
on	O
a	O
bit	O
of	O
quiet	O
painting	O
.	O

Meanwhile	O
the	O
Professor	O
has	O
revealed	O
himself	O
to	O
be	O
an	O
inherently	O
selfish	O
man	O
,	O
while	O
Mr	O
Prout	PERSON
is	O
suddenly	O
far	O
more	O
reasonable	O
.	O

He	O
and	O
Mrs	O
Prout	O
soon	O
resolve	O
their	O
differences	O
,	O
and	O
he	O
tries	O
to	O
be	O
a	O
little	O
more	O
considerate	O
to	O
her.The	O
film	O
ends	O
with	O
the	O
string	O
quartet	O
playing	O
once	O
more	O
and	O
the	O
Captain	O
sitting	O
almost	O
entirely	O
alone	O
in	O
the	O
theatre	O
.	O

